When seasons come, our
hearts will bloom.
Every petal within
shines bright and true.
Plenty will flourish.
Deep in our hearts, we
will bear the mark of
roses of Rome.
Roses of Rome,
let us boom forever.
Roses of Rome, may we
always be with you,
ever. Though
time may fade,
The colors we wear
Our roots stand firm where
glory finds its home Through
every tear, joy
and whispered prayer
We still remain
roses of rose
Roses of rose
Roses of Rome,
let us grow forever
Roses of Rome, may we
always be with you Ever! Good
time make day the colors we wear
Our roots and
fur with glory finds its
homeThrough
every tear, joy and
whispered prayer
We still remain
the roses
of
Rome Roses of
roses Roses of Rome